Polish Junior League of Connecticut Collection CPAA 88.11
Connecticut Polish American Archives
- General Information
  - PJL CT- receipts and disbursement, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - PJL CT- receipts and disbursement, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - PJL CT- fundriser activities., 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - PJL CT- bank check records, 1978-1985 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - PJL CT- bank statements, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - PJL CT- bank statements, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - PJL CT- bank statements, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - PJL CT- bank statements, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - PJL CT- bank statements, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - PJL CT- bank statements, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - PJL CT- bank statements, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - PJL CT- membership list (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - PJL CT - Scrap book containing photographs and newspaper clippings of the PJL's activities., 1926-1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - PJL CT - Scrap book., 1950-1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - PJL CT - Scrap book for the Bal Menuet. Nr. 1., 1954-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - PJL CT - Scrap book for the Bal Menuet. Nr. 2., 1972-1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)